this is the time known as the great pirate era a countless array of pirates go to battle across
the seas in search of the one piece the legendary treasure left behind by gold roger king of the
pirates monkey d luffy a boy whose body turned to rubber after eating the gum gum fruit set sail to
become the next king of the pirates as luffy and his crew conquer numerous obstacles they capture
the unwanted attention of the world government which will use any means necessary to stop them
can't wait to see what kind of adventures up next with a charted course awash in danger and intrigue
the crew will cut a path across the grand line to the new world
after losing his brother ace luffy fell into despair but when he was reminded of his crew
he decided to send them a message that reached across the seas
living through hell sanji's fight for his manhood
on the small sky island of with area there she is we finally found her you fooled us for the last time
it was bad enough that you stole our research notes and tried to run away but you tried with our
feelings as well our hearts forever tainted you'll pay dearly for your treachery you thieving harpy
okay there's our research now and the weather ball in the hostage mr harridus even if you return
everything it's too late for forgiveness i'm so sorry i regret what i've done nobody listen we can't trust
i won't be happy until i punish her with my own two hands punish me how naughty huh
naughty how could you hey stop that you know i didn't mean it in the naughty kind of way i mean we
need to stop talking to her she'll keep making us sound bad did you just try to us you big bully how
cruel of you to pick on me tighten up on the poor girl did you all forget already the stuff she's stolen
misery she's gone oh well quit falling for her trap there must be a mistake i wouldn't do such things
yeah and second thought you seem like a nice young lady those fools don't know what to think anymore do
they ah let's run her off the island once and for all not that i'm sorry i'll never do it again how can
you expect us to trust you it's all right i get it you want me to show you how sorry i am
to win back your trust i'll jump off this island my sacrifice will pay for my offenses goodbye cruel
world idiots what have we done don't be hasty my dear why don't we sit down over a cup of tea
before you do something so drastic farewell okay then as long as you're sorry
now that that's settled i'm gonna stay here a bit longer to learn more about the weather
also my name is nami so stop calling me young lady please first off i'd like a house of my
own to live in everybody needs a little privacy am i right i'll need a bed too and feather pillows
and a nice big bathtub no wait a jacuzzi thanks you guys sky grandpas are the best time to rock and roll
oh
i don't understand you were desperate to get off this island before well i suppose that's your business
Could you refresh my memory?
How does this place work?
Oh, of course.
With area travels on the wind,
traversing the entire world, a little bit slowly.
Now and then, we'll send a few of our scientists
down beneath the clouds to pick up supplies
and gather information.
Information?
Yes, to check our records against others.
Despite all of our research,
there are many mysterious weather conditions in the world
that we've only been able to scratch the surface of.
What?
Pay attention!
Oh, wow.
This is crazy.
Lightning rain?
Indeed, but only on one island.
Quite strange.
It's a terrifying but intriguing sight.
That island is located in the New World.
But of course, if you brave those seas,
then you've got to expect the unexpected
no matter how outlandish it may be.
Ha ha ha ha!
It's a big world out there.
Horridus, please take me as your student.
Teach me all you know about the weather.
Especially in the New World.
Such a desperate plea.
Of course it is.
The lives of my crew members are at stake here, you know?
I'm their only navigator.
And when I'm on that ship, then I take full responsibility.
It's my job to find our way.
And I will not let my captain down no matter what it takes.
That's because Luffy wants to become the King of the Pirates.
To help him, I need to be the best navigator the world has ever seen.
Sounds like your captain is very lucky.
He has such a thoughtful and clever crewmate.
Yeah, I have to be.
What does that mean?
Well, he is determined and he's reliable as a captain.
But he doesn't know anything about the sea.
He's so ridiculous, without my help, he would be lost.
Luffy, please help me.
He's gonna pay!
I owe him that he's such a pain.
Huh?
I mean, he's real high-maintenance.
Good!
Then you two balance each other out.
And I want to give him all the help he needs.
Just like he helped me.
Anyway, can you tell me about the Weather Ball?
Well, it's complicated.
One of Witheria's masterpieces, but quite delicate.
You must be careful.
Misuse it, and the whole world could go topsy-turvy.
Can it be used as a weapon, then?
Hey, why are you even asking that?
Hmm.
Quit smiling.
Ha, ha, ha.
Gnomi!
You'll always be my friend!
Woo!
Meanwhile, on the Mechanical Island, in the future land,
the
Baltimore.
Nothing new on the surprise bombing at Dr. Vegapunk's lab.
We still haven't found the culprit.
Hey!
Hurry up!
It was, without exaggeration, the greatest loss of our time.
Have you heard anything at all?
Well, rumor has it that one of the intruders looks a lot like a gorilla, if you can believe
that.
Sorry, that's pretty hard to believe.
I don't think he made it all the way to the harbor.
You can't reach that end of the island unless you've got something that can break through
all this ice.
Only our ships have that kind of equipment.
People are claiming the intruder was none other than Cyborg Frankie of the Straw Hat Pirates.
But the only place he's been spotted the past month is the Sabauri Archipelago, and
there's no way he could have made it to Baltimore from all the way over there.
Captain Gorilla, that's heard.
Are you kidding me?
No, I didn't.
I didn't.
You can't.
I was just kidding.
But the only place he's been spotted the past month
is the Sabaori Archipelago.
And there's no way he could have made it to Baltimore
from all the way over there.
Captain Gorilla, the search team is about to head to the mountains.
Tell them to wait.
I'll be there shortly.
What's this?
The explosion must have uncovered a hidden entrance.
Now, that's a surprise.
I've never heard of such a thing.
I can hardly believe it.
Dr. Vegapunk had another laboratory,
right under our notice.
This must be where he made all the cyborg animals
that worked on his projects.
Don't break anything!
You are the last person I want to hear that from!
I admit, I did blow away some valuable stuff.
But it was mostly knick-knacks and gadgets,
things to improve your quality of life.
That's nice, but it's not what I need.
I'm more interested in the weapons he designed,
the ones he's got right here.
This is insane.
There's everything from battleships to bio-creatures.
And this is the place where he cooked it up day after day.
All right, it's settled.
I'm gonna live here!
Huh? Here?
Yeah!
The thing is, I'm still gonna need cola and stuff.
So I hope you guys don't mind if I come by to visit you sometimes.
It's not that bad.
As long as you keep this a secret, I won't cause trouble,
and trouble won't find me.
So do we have a deal?
What is wrong with you three?
It's just my face!
Don't look at us!
There!
Is this better?
That's not so bad.
Frankie!
Excuse me.
It's cold in here.
Then put on some pants.
Perfect.
Now it's nice and warm.
You're still not wearing any of those clothes.
You're not wearing any of those clothes.
I'm not wearing any of those clothes.
This doesn't make sense. Didn't you say that you wanted to get off this island?
Maybe before, but...
My dream.
It would be my honor if you'd take my ship and sail across the world!
Luffy, because of you, I was able to hold on to my dream.
Frankie! Thanks! The ship is great! Just like you said, it's the best! We'll take good care of it!
Oh, I hate to break it to you, but if you want your undies back, then you're gonna have to join our crew!
To think I almost turned you down. I might have spent the rest of my life without seeing the world.
Who knows how many seas we'll cross, and what kind of trouble we'll get into along the way.
But when we reach the end of our voyage, I can truly call our ship the Ship of Dreams.
So listen up, Luffy. The Thousand Sunny isn't giving up. Not ever.
And as her captain, I know you aren't giving up either. So let's sail.
I'm gonna study my cold, hairy butt off. When you see me again, I'll be more super than ever!
Hold on tight, Luffy. Our adventure's just begun!
Uh, hey! Your tiger's on fire!
Huh?
Ow, ow, ow! Put it out! Put it out!
Hey, what was that?
A monster! Stand your ground!
That's right, Luffy. Leave it to me. Together, we'll conquer the seas of the New World.
This day, a legend was born. And for many years to come, people would speak in hushed voices of the burning beasts.
The burning beast of Baltimore.
In the Kamabaka Kingdom, on the Grand Line.
Say, what was the article that caught your attention in the paper?
Roger that.
Odd. It seems to have calmed you down.
A message from Luffy. A hidden message in the newspaper that only his friends would understand. Wanna know what it is?
Oh, wait! You don't believe I'm his friend to begin with, so I'm not gonna tell you!
You think you're cute, huh?
Hey, this meal is pretty good. Who cooked it?
What a pleasant surprise! You have quite the discriminating palate.
It's weird, though. Suddenly, I feel like there's this energy flowing through me.
That's because you just ate a dish of aggression!
Ha! Such creations are this island's specialty!
Yes! Yes! Yes! Yes! Yes! Yes!
Ah! Behold! The chiseled muscles on my lovely candies here are works of art!
Ooh!
They belie their gentle hearts. How did my candies become so lovely? By eating the dishes of aggression!
You are what you eat! Body, mind, and soul! Food holds the key to keeping it all healthy!
For example, if all people in the world drank a glass of milk every day...
There would be less crime! It's perfectly logical!
In other words, aggression is good!
The food you eat can build your body?
Can't say I've ever thought of approaching it that way before.
Those candies of his. If they could build muscle, I wonder what else is possible with that food.
Whoa! Does that mean I could cook sexy food and make Robin and Nami even hotter than they are now?
Cause that sounds awesome!
What are we gonna do with this guy?
What do I do with myself?
That settles it!
You gotta teach me this magic food thing now!
Yeah, you wish!
Hold your horses, Buster! You have to earn it!
Listen, there are 99 vital recipes in all!
There are many new Kama Kenpo techniques, but this one is passed down as a form of bridal training!
The secrets of Kamabaka Kingdom don't get shared with just any randy scum that makes their way to us!
If you want to learn our recipes, we need the heart of a true maiden!
And these ladies would love to teach you!
Not a chance!
Sorry to disappoint, but I'm not here to be gal pals with your freaky little friends!
I was born to love the most beautiful ladies in the world!
Not...
Yee-haw!
Well, quirks aside, you've got guts, boy. I like you, so that means I'll give you a chance.
Oh, yeah?
But a chance is just a chance!
Because I'll be giving the recipes to the 99 Grand Masters of New Kama Kenpo on this island!
If you're half the man you think you are, you can defeat them and claim the recipes for yourself!
Also, do not let your guard down, because every new Kama on the island will be trying to put this adorable dress on you!
Hope you have fun protecting your fragile manhood!
Oh, Sanjay!
Say goodbye to sleeping!
This sweet dress! If you've never worn one before, you're in for a treat!
They're so breathable!
Join us!
It's nice to be girly.
It's just you versus the island of New Kama Kenpo! Let's begin!
If you can win this fight, I'll also throw in a ship! Not a bad deal, if you ask me.
So what do you say, boy?
So listen, Mr. Cook, why don't you leave this boat and join my crew?
Huh?
I could use a cook like you on my pirate ship!
I'm not worried.
Hmph.
Because I don't think it's time for me to die just yet!
I've seen one or two like him before.
Stubborn kids who'd rather die than have to turn away from a fight once it's started.
I don't believe I've heard an answer. Could it be that you've given up already?
Well, if you quit, then win?
When I win this?
Huh?
When I finish beating all of them?
I bet I'll be a whole lot stronger than I am now.
Even with a hundred thousand more weapons, I'll be a whole lot stronger than I am now.
Even with a hundred thousand more weapons, our chore boy will win.
I'll be a whole lot stronger than I am now.
Even with a hundred thousand more weapons, I'll be a whole lot stronger than I am now.
I don't believe I've heard an answer.
Could it be that you've given up already?
Well, if you quit, then win...
When I win this, when I finish beating all of them, I bet I'll be a whole lot stronger
than I am now.
Even with a hundred thousand more weapons, our chore boy can still bring him to his knees
because he does not know fear.
Hey, Luffy, hang in there just a little while longer.
I promised myself that one of these days, I'll go to the Grand Line.
Well, let's go right now!
It just isn't the right time, not yet.
Say, have you ever heard of the All-Blue?
No.
You've got to be kidding me. That sea is a miracle.
Your dream is foolish.
Then again, so's mine.
Now is as good a time as any.
Why not start my quest right now?
Sanji.
I'll be joining your little crew on your journey to be King of the Pirates.
Do you hear me, Luffy?
I want to be your cook.
Luffy, when we meet again,
you'll see.
I'll be the best damn chef in all of the New World.
I'll make food fit for the King of the Pirates.
Until then,
I must survive
this hell.
I accept your challenge.
Now give me your worst.
That's better.
Remember, we're not going easy on you.
Just shut up and fight.
You heard him, lady.
Go to town!
Hey, Sanji!
Oh, don't give me the cold shoulder!
Cannon!
How feisty!
Pull it together.
I can't lose yet.
Not to you.
That wasn't nice.
Luffy, both of us are getting through this no matter what it takes.
So, I heard you're fighting me for my recipe.
Well, Caroline is ready.
Come and get it if you dare.
This is convenient.
After that last battle we had, I owe you a proper beatdown.
Here I come!
Make no mistake, I will win!
With their reunion on hold, each member of the Straw Hat crew finds a new goal to strive for.
Thankfully, their surroundings are ripe with opportunity.
Determined to push forward into the new world, they vow to show their captain a new strength the next time they meet.
On the next One Piece, I will get much, much stronger!
Zoro's pledged to his captain, I'm gonna be king of the pirates!